DAVID LEIGHTON

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

 enleightond@gmail.com enleightond.com 510.388.8046 Oakland, CA. in enleightond O enleightond

SUMMARY

Software developer with an animation background and over 15 years of IT support and project management expertise. Merging my experience of technology and creative design is my passion and career focus. I excel in team collaboration and customer service. I bring excellent trouble-shooting, organizational, and leadership skills to any project. While I thrive in team environments, I have a strong ability to work independently, and build new skill sets to accommodate any project.

EDUCATION

Galvanize

A 24 week immersive web development bootcamp

Skill set focused on HTML, CSS, Javascript, AngularJS, Node/Express, SQL(Knex, Posgres), Github, Bootstrap

Capella Education

A 4 week immersive study of User Interface and User Experience design concepts focusing on Responsive Web Design

Ex'pression College

PROJECTS

Portfolio

- A little bit about me and my projects.
- JavaScript | AngularJS | HTML | CSS.
- https://github.com/enleightond/enleightond.github.io

Twitch Me

- This single page app takes the popular twitch ty experience and gives a customized, streamlined experience to view streaming content.
- ${\sf JavaScript \mid HTML \mid CSS \mid PostgreSql \mid Express \mid Angular JS \mid Bcrypt \ and \ OAuth2}.$

MeanTea

- A shopping cart app selling a tea product experience.
- JavaScript | HTML | CSS | PostgreSql | Express | AngularJS on the front end

Epic Events

- A group project in which we created an event aggregate.
- JavaScript | HTML | CSS | AngularJS, ProstgreSql, Express. OAuth2.

EMPLOYMENT

BlackRock, Senior IT Support Technician | Systems, San Francisco, CA.

Mar 2015 - Oct 2015

- Senior Level Deskside Support Technician
- Managing Microsoft Office 365 migration as an Enterprise level project
- Extensive troubleshooting, documentation and collaboration of numerous teams to allow for a smooth and efficient transition.

 Bloomberg | Trade floor software/hardware support | Microsoft Office 365 support | Blackberry Enterprise Server | Mobile device support (iOS/Android) | VPN networks | Windows 7 desktop support

abcISP.inc, Senior IT Administrator, Help Desk | Systems, Emeryville, CA.

Mar 2013 - Feb 2014

- Managed the local office technical needs of the client, Zogenix, located in Emeryville, CA.
- Initiated, and successfully implemented the upgrade/migration of the aging VPN network to comply with security and infrastructure needs for the Zogenix client for all domestic, international, and remote users
- Managed Microsoft Office 365 migration for mid sized client local office
- Server maintenance and backups | Remote user support | Microsoft Office 365 support | Blackberry Enterprise Server | Mobile device support (iOS/Android) | VPN networks | Windows 7 desktop support

Working Assets | CREDO Mobile, IT Help Desk Administrator | Systems Engineering, San Francisco, CA.

Sep 2008 - Jul 2012

- Desktop Support for the mid size company, managed 90%+ of all Help Desk support related issues for 150+ local and remote user: Coordinated company wide Microsoft Operating System migration from WinXp to Win7
- Server administration/maintenance/backup using Comm-Vault Backup Solution Server | Active Directory maintenance (2003/2008/2010 Exchange 2008/2010) | Blackberry Enterprise Server | VMWare ESXi | ESX Sharepoint 2008 Server GFI LanGuard. Organized and documented Software licensing compliance.

 Anti-Virus security management: McAffe ePO | Kapersky Security Center | WebSense monitoring and remediation.
- Performed new employee systems and security orientations. Complete overhaul of aging Meridian phone system to digital Avaya phone system and server with continued server and client system administration.
- Managed and administrated conference rooms, systems | A/V equipment
- Hardware and Software purchasing management.
 Created a complete company computer system Inventory Control

AutumnMoon Entertainment, 3D Character Animator, Petaluma, CA.

Mar 2007 - Mar 2008

- Principal Character Animator for PC adventure video game Completed animation project from inception to completion
- Assisted in lighting, rendering, and layout design.
- Created and assisted Animation Lead in asset creation pipeline and asset management using SVN.
- Assisted Animation Lead in animation quality assurance.
 Performed technical duties relating to rendering farm system as needed.

SKILLS

DEVELOPMENT: Javascript | HTML | CSS | GitHub | AngularJS | Bootstrap | PHP | C# | JQuery | NodeExpress | SQL(Knex, Posgres) | UI/UX | Responsive Web ANIMATION: Traditional and 3D animation | Layout | Lighting | Texturing | Maya | Photoshop CS | Editing | Composition INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY:

Windows | Mac | Linex | Bash | Server | Hardware | Software | Active Directory | Blackberry | Bloomberg | Trade Floor | Comm Vault Backup | GFI Langaurd | Group Policy | Anti - Virus | VPN | VMware |, Project management | System Administration | IT Operations | System Engineering | TCP/IP | Inventory Management | QA/Testing | Databases | Knowledge base